DAVID MCINTYRE

- **1** 017645945439
- davidrobert.mcintyre@gmail.com
- Seestraße 106, Berlin, 13353
- @davidxmcintyre

PROFILE

I am a filmmaking graduate with many years of experience in the hospitality industry as both a bartender and barista. I also have a wealth of experience in supervisory and management roles. In my free time I have also become a published writer and poet.

SKILLS

- Problem Solving
- Barista Training
- · Camera Skills
- Video Editing
- Photography
- English (Native)
- German (A.2)
- Bar Training

EXPERIENCE

BARTENDER / ASSISTANT MANAGER (FROM 2018)

The Castle Berlin

2017 - 2023

- Assistant the General Manager in any delegated tasks
- Ensure smooth running of shifts
- Ordering and rotating stock
- · Training of new team members

BARISTA MAESTRO

Costa Coffee

2015 - 2017

- Operate coffee machine to high standards
- Serve customers in a prompt, friendly manner
- Ensure brand standards are adhered to

EDUCATION

SECONDARY SCHOOL

Auchenharvie Academy

2004 - 2010

BA FILMMAKING & SCREENWRITING

University of the West of Scotland

2010 - 2014

FREELANCE VIDEOGRAPHER

Self Employed Freelance

2014 - 2017

- Build a client base
- Ensure high-quality film and/or editing
- Deliver a high standard, professional product